So this is, we can say the difference that Gemini has.
And this is the best use case.
And the best time that you can use Gemini and the best case,
you know, especially when it comes to,
as I said, other Google products.
And when you want your AI to be compatible
with the other products of Google,
like when it comes to using Gemini on a daily basis
and you have an Android phone, right?
So Gemini is a great AI option
because it's very compatible with Android
because both are owned by the same company,
if that makes sense, you know?
Already comes to YouTube.
So you have a YouTube video that you want to analyze
or you want to find the best videos
on a very specific topic on YouTube.
So you want to do YouTube search in general.
Well, Gemini is a great option again
because it's from Google and YouTube is from Google, you know?
So these two come from the same mother.
And that's pretty much all when it comes to the use edges
and the use cases for this very tool.